[Wu Ren, Ningcheng Police Station]
Master,
why
are you trying to kill me?
Once the student learns everything,
the master starves.
Look at all you've accomplished
at such a young age.
And now you want to take my place?
In your dreams.
Tianbail.
Rest easy.
Once the student learns everything,
the master starves.
And now you want to take my place?
In your dreams.
[Eclipse in the Lost City]
[Episode 3]
A teacher
is a father for life.
All these years,
I never once thought of taking his place.
Yet he did that to me.
Wu Ren
looks like an honorable man,
but he's even more ruthless than we are.
No wonder
you're willing to join a gang
just to get your revenge.
But don't worry.
As long as you join our Shisha Gang,
killing Wu Ren
would be easy.
However,
as long as that mole
in the Qingtian Gang is alive,
our Shisha Gang
will always have a weakness
in their hands.
We've made a deal.
Find him
and kill him.
Consider it your initiation.
Once you do that,
you'll be one of us.
Don't worry, Mr. Hui.
I've got this.
Then I'll wait for your good news.
When the time comes,
don't go soft.
If he won't show me any loyalty...
I won't show him any either.
[Lu Mansion]
Young Master.
Only the heads of our four branches
could have been poisoning
the old chief over time.
You?
No way.
Baihu died protecting the old man,
so we can rule him out, too.
That leaves only Qinglong and Zhuque.
Find a chance to bring them in
and question them properly.
What if they refuse to come?
It's not up to them.
Give this to Zhuque.
Tell her I'll hand out
the gang leader's tokens.
She will definitely come.
I understand.
Although Zhuque has established
her own faction,
she has always struggled
to win people over.
If she has the chief's token,
it'll help her establish some authority.
Exactly.
With smart people,
it's better to win them over
with incentives.
What about Qinglong?
Qinglong is a brute.
We'll have to force him.
The old man once told me
he kept a ledger in Master Qi's pawnshop.
It records
all his shady dealings
with Ningcheng's top officials.
Once it's exposed,
those people won't spare him.
I understand.
You want to get the ledger from Master Qi
and use it to force Qinglong to show up.
But Master Qi is not easy to deal with.
Even the old chief
got burned by him a few times.
What are you afraid of?
I've got a secret weapon.
Miss.
This is a fine piece of jade.
But...
I can only offer this much.
Where is Master Qi?
It's really unfortunate.
He is not here today.
How about you come back another day?
It's fine.
I'll wait for him.
I can only offer this much
for this jade...
Please offer a little more.
This jade has
such beautiful color and clarity.
It's good enough to be a family heirloom.
And you only offer this much?
I'll give you two silver dollars for it.
You...
Thank you, Boss.
This watch...
This watch is a British brand too,
isn't it?
It's gone up in value lately.
It's worth 30 silver dollars.
What?
The shopkeeper said it's only worth
2 silver dollars.
You believe him?
I am the shopkeeper.
He's Young Master Lu
of the Qingtian Gang.
He has seen so many good things.
He definitely knows his stuff.
I'm not selling this watch anymore.
You...
What a lousy pawnshop.
They prey on people
when they're desperate for money.
Come and take a look, everyone!
Lu Ye.
What exactly do you want?
Master Qi.
You're finally willing to see me.
[Master Qi, Ningcheng Pawnshop]
Master Qi.
I heard Qinglong left a ledger with you.
He's been using my old man's name
to cause trouble everywhere.
The Qingtian Gang should be the ones
handling this ledger.
Qingtian Gang?
What a joke.
Does the Qingtian Gang even exist anymore?
Young Master Lu.
I'll give you one chance.
Walk out of here on your own.
Fine.
It seems you're determined
not to give it to me.
So what if I am?
Let me make this clear.
If you've got the guts,
send the cops to come get it.
Are you serious?
Hand it over.
Officer...
Officer Shen.
How did you...
Is this how you treat your guests?
My servants don't know any better.
Let me do it.
Master Qi.
What about the ledger?
Sure, we can work something out.
But I need to look for it.
No problem.
I'll just have a little chat
with your wife.
I wonder
if she knows about your illegitimate child
in the suburbs.
Don't...
Young Master Lu.
I'll go get it right now.
[Ledger]
Alright.
I won't bother you then.
Tianbai!
Why is he here?
You brat.
You made me lose face.
Don't think I'll let you off easy, either.
Here we go.
Tianbai.
I'm glad you're okay.
I was so worried about you.
Lu Ye.
What did you do to him?
Officer Wu.
Calm down.
Look.
He's standing right in front of you,
isn't he?
I won't let you get away with this.
I swear to God
I didn't harm him.
At least...
I didn't throw him into the fire,
steal his credit,
and use him as a stepping stone
to get ahead.
Tianbai.
Don't believe him.
He is your sworn enemy.
He is lying to you.
Right.
Look.
This is your police badge.
Come on.
Go back with me.
I will help you remember slowly.
Is it okay?
It seems
he really thinks
I don't remember anything.
Why are you looking at me?
It's up to you.
If you want to leave, then leave.
I don't know you.
You should leave.
Lu Ye!
Tianbai, you...
Take one more step,
and I won't hold back.
All right.
Don't scare Officer Wu.
Put it down.
[Ningcheng Police Station]
Shen Tianbai,
you're actually still alive.
I'll find a way to finish you off.
[See you at the train station at 4 p.m.
Come alone. ]
[Otherwise, you'll be collecting
Lu Ye's body in 3 days.]
Young Master,
we've got a problem.
Shen Tianbai has gone out.
What?
He went to the train station.
Our people said Wu Ren
asked him to meet him there.
Let's go.
There really is something going on
between them.
Shen Tianbai,
you won't get away.
I knew
you would definitely come.
Young Master,
he's inside.
Don't forget
I taught you all of this.
Go to hell!
[Ningcheng Train Station]
After him!
Are you still alive?
Young Master.
Why did you come here?
Because of this.
See you at the train station at 4 p.m.
Come alone.
Otherwise,
you'll be collecting Lu Ye's body
in 3 days.
You did it just for this?
Do you have any brains at all?
He wanted to kill you.
Did you think about...
I couldn't risk it.
I couldn't
risk your life
It's getting late.
Let's go home.
Yes.
Lu Ye,
you've tested me so many times.
This time,
you should finally believe me.
Young Master,
do you really trust Shen Tianbai?
What do you think?
You...
You still don't trust him.
If so,
why did you save him?
Because
I want him to trust me.
The night is still young.